# Olivia Hu

Graphic Designer and Website Designer

Hi, I'm Olivia! I am a junior at Parsons School of Design studying a BFA in Communication Design. I do graphic design, website design, branding, and illustration. I'm interested in creating unique experiences through design and interaction.





www.imoliviahu.com



Oct 2020-Dec 2020

July 2021-August 2021

## **SKILLS**

Photoshop	Creative
InDesign	Organized
Illustrator	Collaboration
Premiere Pro	Typography
Social Media	Website Design
HTML & CSS	UI/UX
Figma	Branding
Google Suite	Illustration
Microsoft Office	Photography

## **EDUCATION**

Parsons School of Design, The New School	August 2020-present
Communication Design BFA (GPA: 3.9)	
CS50: Introduction to Computer Science	June 2020-August 2020
Harvard edX Online Course	
Sharron Art Center	June 2020-August 2020
Refined my fundamental art skills through sketching, painting, and sculpture.	

# **LANGUAGES**

English	•••••
Chinese	••••••
Snanish	••••

## **WORK EXPERIENCE**

Yeh IDeology & Thrive By Design | Creative Intern May 2022-August 2022 Developed the layout, information structure, branding, language, animations, typography, and color scheme of Yeh IDeology's Thrive By Design website. Created monthly newsletters with motion graphics and writing for Yeh IDeology.

Youth and Sustainability | Brand & Website Designer March 2022-April 2022 Created the logo, colors, and typography for brand while collaborating with a team. Coded mobile version of website with HTML, CSS, and Javascript.

### **INTERESTS**





#### Embolden Jewelry | Branding and Content Designer June 2020-August 2022

Created logo, designed promotional graphics, photographed jewelry and developed Instagram profile/feed. Designed the layout, structure, color scheme, images, and typography of website.

#### Dancing Movies



## Portfolio Editor and Photographer | Freelance

Assisted multiple art students by photographing and editing their artworks for art contests and developing college art portfolios.





# Starbucks | Barista

Memorized and crafted beverages in a fast-paced working environment while communicating with coworkers and customers to facilitate the best experience.







Trave



Comics

# **AWARDS**

National Medal from Scholastic Art and Writing Awards 2020 High Merit Student Award from Celebrating Art Contest 2019 & 2020